<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prepare the GCP Environment on JFrog DevOps on GCP Workshop</title>
    <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/clouddays/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prepare the GCP Environment on JFrog DevOps on GCP Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://jfrogtraining.github.io/clouddays/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Get a GCP Environment</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/clouddays/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/411_get_gcp_environment.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/clouddays/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/411_get_gcp_environment.html</guid>
      <description>This workshop requires a GCP environment. Your instructor will provide a link and an activation code. The following steps walk through the process of obtaining a GCP environment using the provided link and activation code.
When using this temporary GCP environment, use an Incognito Window to avoid conflicts with your existing Google Account.
  Open the instructor provided link in your browser. This will take you to environment registration page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download the Workshop Code</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/clouddays/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/412_download_workshop_code.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/clouddays/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/412_download_workshop_code.html</guid>
      <description>The workshop code is located at https://github.com/jfrogtraining/clouddays GitHub repository. We will clone this repository locally in order to pull the required workshop files and scripts. In your Google Cloud Shell, clone this repository to your local directory with the following command.
git clone https://github.com/jfrogtraining/clouddays.git</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a GKE Cluster</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/clouddays/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/413_create_gke_cluster.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/clouddays/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/413_create_gke_cluster.html</guid>
      <description>In this section, we will create a GKE Cluster in our Google Cloud Shell using the gcloud CLI.
The gcloud command-line interface is the primary CLI tool to create and manage Google Cloud resources. You can use this tool to perform many common platform tasks either from the command line or in scripts and other automations.
  In your Google Cloud Shell, execute the following command to set an environment variable for the GCP environment project ID.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
