<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Supply Chain Security on JFrog DevOps on GCP Workshop</title>
    <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software Supply Chain Security on JFrog DevOps on GCP Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JFrog Platform for DevSecOps in the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud/24_jfrog_platform_overview.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud/24_jfrog_platform_overview.html</guid>
      <description>The JFrog Platform is designed to meet the growing needs of companies to develop and distribute a secure software in the cloud. It provides DevOps teams with the tools needed to create, manage, secure and deploy software with ease. These tools cover everything from continuous integration and delivery (CI/CD), binary repository management, artifact maturity, security and vulnerability protection (DevSecOps), release management, analytics and distribution.
With the JFrog DevOps Platform — and in particular with JFrog Artifactory, JFrog Xray and JFrog Distribution , you can easily get all the granular data you need for an SBOM, including:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud for DevSecOps</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud/24_gcp_ci_cd.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud/24_gcp_ci_cd.html</guid>
      <description>Continuous integration and delivery (CI/CD) is the process by which your software components are built from code, integrated with dependencies, tested, released, and deployed to end-users. Self managed CI/CD pipelines put infrastructure strain on platform teams, which leads to queue times for developers. Google Cloud provides fully managed services which scale up and down to meet demand, including:
 Google Cloud Build - flexible platform for developer automation, including capabilities to build and test container and non-container artifacts Google Cloud Deploy - purpose-built continuous delivery with approval gates for GCP runtimes, including GKE.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
