<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JFrog DevOps on GCP Workshop</title>
    <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JFrog DevOps on GCP Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud/23_dev_sec_ops.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud/23_dev_sec_ops.html</guid>
      <description>Any security issue identified by a security scanning may be reviewed by a small security team that may lack the technical knowledge. This challenge can be reduced by shifting left to the developer and operations teams, making them also responsible for security and compliance. This moves security earlier in the software delivery process. Source code, dependency and artifact security scanning are some examples of moving security into the development process. Implementing the identification of security issues earlier in the CI/CD pipeline, as well as automating security and compliance policies in the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC), rather than using manual processes, is crucial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JFrog Platform for DevSecOps in the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud/24_jfrog_platform_overview.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud/24_jfrog_platform_overview.html</guid>
      <description>The JFrog Platform is designed to meet the growing needs of companies to develop and distribute a secure software in the cloud. It provides DevOps teams with the tools needed to create, manage, secure and deploy software with ease. These tools cover everything from continuous integration and delivery (CI/CD), binary repository management, artifact maturity, security and vulnerability protection (DevSecOps), release management, analytics and distribution.
With the JFrog DevOps Platform — and in particular with JFrog Artifactory, JFrog Xray and JFrog Distribution , you can easily get all the granular data you need for an SBOM, including:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud for DevSecOps</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud/24_gcp_ci_cd.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/2_devops_cloud/24_gcp_ci_cd.html</guid>
      <description>Continuous integration and delivery (CI/CD) is the process by which your software components are built from code, integrated with dependencies, tested, released, and deployed to end-users. Self managed CI/CD pipelines put infrastructure strain on platform teams, which leads to queue times for developers. Google Cloud provides fully managed services which scale up and down to meet demand, including:
 Google Cloud Build - flexible platform for developer automation, including capabilities to build and test container and non-container artifacts Google Cloud Deploy - purpose-built continuous delivery with approval gates for GCP runtimes, including GKE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build the JFrog CLI Docker Image</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/5_build_publish_app/51_build_jfrog_cli_image.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/5_build_publish_app/51_build_jfrog_cli_image.html</guid>
      <description>First, we will use Google Cloud Build to create a npm docker image with the JFrog CLI. This will enable us to use JFrog CLI to build npm packages.
Google Cloud Build uses Docker to execute builds. For each build step, Cloud Build executes a Docker container as an instance of docker run.
   Return to your Cloud Shell terminal and change directory to gcp-gke-workshop/jfrog-cli-docker.
  We will use Google Cloud Build to create JFrog CLI docker image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build and Deploy the NPM Application Docker Image</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/5_build_publish_app/52_build_docker_image.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/5_build_publish_app/52_build_docker_image.html</guid>
      <description>Now, we can use new JFrog CLI image to build the NPM application Docker image and push it to Artifactory&amp;rsquo;s Docker repository using Cloud Build Trigger.
  Return to your Google Cloud Shell terminal and change directory to gcp-gke-workshop/workshop-app.
  Use Google Cloud Build, trigger and the JFrog CLI to build the NPM Docker image. The cloud build trigger uses cloudbuild.yaml. If you look inside this file, you will find it performs following steps:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get a GCP Environment</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/411_get_gcp_environment.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/411_get_gcp_environment.html</guid>
      <description>If you have your own Google account and have your own GCP environment, skip this step.
 This workshop requires a GCP environment. If this is a JFrog and Google hosted event, your instructor will provide a link and an activation code. The following steps walk through the process of obtaining a GCP environment using the provided link and activation code. Otherwise, use your own GCP environment and skip this step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download the Workshop Code</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/412_download_workshop_code.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/412_download_workshop_code.html</guid>
      <description>The workshop code is located at https://github.com/jfrogtraining/gcp-gke-workshop GitHub repository. We will fork this repo and then clone locally in order to pull the required workshop files and scripts.
 Click on the Google Cloud Shell button at the top right of the console to open Google Cloud Shell terminal in your browser.  Click the Continue button and wait a few moments for you Google Cloud Shell Machine to be ready.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create GKE Clusters</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/413_create_gke_cluster.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/413_create_gke_cluster.html</guid>
      <description>In this section, we will create GKE Clusters in our Google Cloud Shell using the gcloud CLI.
The gcloud command-line interface is the primary CLI tool to create and manage Google Cloud resources. You can use this tool to perform many common platform tasks either from the command line or in scripts and other automations.
  In your Google Cloud Shell, execute the following command to set an environment variable for the GCP environment project ID.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Cloud Deploy Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/414_cloud_deploy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/414_cloud_deploy.html</guid>
      <description>In this section, we will create a Cloud Deploy pipeline to deploy our app in test, stage and prod environments.
  First select Cloud Deploy from your product catalog and enable it if it&amp;rsquo;s already not enabled.
  Execute the following command to add clouddeploy.jobRunner role to the serice account.
  gcloud projects add-iam-policy-binding $PROJECT_ID \ --member=serviceAccount:$(gcloud projects describe $PROJECT_ID \ --format=&amp;quot;value(projectNumber)&amp;quot;)-compute@developer.gserviceaccount.com \ --role=&amp;quot;roles/clouddeploy.jobRunner&amp;quot; Now execute the below command to add the Kubernetes Developer permissions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Cloud Build Trigger</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/415_cloud_trigger.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/41_gcp_environment_setup/415_cloud_trigger.html</guid>
      <description>In this section, we will create a Cloud Build trigger which will trigger automatically the cloud build file on any push to the github repo and deploy to test.
  Go to https://github.com/jfrogtraining/gcp-gke-workshop and fork this repo.
  Navigate to Cloud Buiild and select Triggers from the left pane.
  Click on + CREATE TRIGGER and give it a name workshop.
  Select CONNECT NEW REPOSITORY in source, which will take you to authenticate your github repo from where you want to trigger cloud build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get a Free JFrog Platform Instance</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/421_jfrog_free.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/421_jfrog_free.html</guid>
      <description>If you do not have access to a JFrog Platform instance, use the JFrog Platform Cloud Free Tier to get your own JFrog Platform instance with Artifactory and Xray.
When signing up for the JFrog Platform Cloud Free Tier, ensure that you select Google Cloud.
  JFrog Platform Cloud Free Tier   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generate an API Key</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/422_api_key.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/422_api_key.html</guid>
      <description>Remember your username and API key. We will use it again with the JFrog CLI and to set up GKE to deploy your image.
  Go to your JFrog Platform instance at https://[server name].jfrog.io. Refer to your JFrog Free Subscription Activation email if needed. Substitute your server name.  Login to your JFrog Platform instance with your credentials.  Once logged into your JFrog Platform instance, you will be presented with the landing page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create NPM and Docker Repos</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/423_create_repos.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/423_create_repos.html</guid>
      <description>Next, we will set up a NPM and Docker repositories in Artifactory.
 In your JFrog Platform instance go to Administration ► Repositories ► Repositories.  Click on New Local Repository on the right.  For package type, select Docker.  Specify clouddays for the Repository Key.   Click Create Local Repository.
  Next, we must create NPM repositories that will be used for NPM dependencies. JFrog provides an easy Quick Setup option for this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a sceret for access token in Secret Manager</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/424_create_access_token_secret.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/424_create_access_token_secret.html</guid>
      <description>We will now create an admin access token and use that token to store as secret in Secret Manager in GCP, which will be used by Cloud Build.
  In your JFrog Platform instance go to Administration ► Identity and Access ► Access Tokens.
  Click on Generate Token, enter the User name and click on Generate. Copy and save the generated token somewhere.
  Now go to your GCP console and search for Secret Manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure a Xray Index</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/425_configure_xray_index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/425_configure_xray_index.html</guid>
      <description>First we will have to enable Xray if its not already enabled, for that go to package view Application ► Artifactory ► Packages. Click on any package and go to Xray Data and click on enable xray.
  Let&amp;rsquo;s configure Xray to index the new Docker repository automatically. Go to Administration ► Xray ► Settings.
   Click on Indexed Resources.
  Click on Add a Repository on the right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Xray Policy</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/426_create_xray_policy.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/426_create_xray_policy.html</guid>
      <description>Next, we will create an Xray security policy that sets the types of security violations to alert on.
 Go to Administration ► Xray ► Watches &amp;amp; Policies ► Policies.   Click on Create a Policy.
  Give the policy a name like default-security and a description.
   Click on New Rule at the right.
  Give the rule a name like high-security-rule.
  For Minimal Severity, specify High.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Xray Watch</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/427_create_xray_watch.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/4_workshop_setup/42_jfrog_setup/427_create_xray_watch.html</guid>
      <description>Next, we will create an Xray security watch to scan our new Docker repository.
 Go to Administration ► Xray ► Watches &amp;amp; Policies ► Watches.   Click on Set up a Watch.
  Give the watch a name like clouddays-docker-repo-watch and a description.
   Click on Add Repositories.
  Move the clouddays repository into the Included Repositories.
   Click Save.
  Scroll down to the Assigned Policies and click on Manage Policies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleanup</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/cleanup.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/cleanup.html</guid>
      <description>Your JFrog Platform Instance - The JFrog Platform instance that you used in this workshop will automatically be destroyed after the workshop. There isn&amp;rsquo;t anything you need to do. If you would like keep it, you can upgrade to one of the premium plans. Do this by clicking on the Upgrade button.   GKE Cluster - To cleanup your GKE resources, go to your GKE console and delete following resources</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/resources.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jfrogtraining.github.io/gcp-gke-workshop/resources.html</guid>
      <description>JFrog Platform Documentation - The full documentation of the JFrog Platform, the universal, hybrid, end-to-end DevOps automation solution. It is designed to take you through all the JFrog Products. Including user, administration and developer guides, installation and upgrade procedures, system architecture and configuration, and working with the JFrog application. JFrog Academy - Learn more about the JFrog Platform at your own pace with JFrog Academy free courses taught by our experts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
